<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[BodyBuildingCooperative]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[BodyBuildingCooperative]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/bodybuildingcooperative/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 07:53:48 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/bodybuildingcooperative/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8ba2517d-4017-40d7-a8d3-4b4e77558e7d.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bodybuildingcooperative/3a9c91bf-fcad-46a7-b93e-ce5e294fd65d/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3a9c91bf-fcad-46a7-b93e-ce5e294fd65d</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 07:47:14 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Our Story]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Our Story</h1><h2>from a simple question to an even simpler answer...</h2><p>While studying together at the University of Victoria- Adam Kammer (Art Major), Scott Peris (Business Major), and Sean Holler (Political Science Major) discussed over dinner why nutritional supplements were so damn expensive. They had always assumed it was because companies sourced the highest quality ingriedents, had large research and development budgets and vast teams of employees. What they found was that this was almost never the case. The bulk of money was actually spent on advertising, marketing strategies, and signing professional athletes. Soon after discussing it, an idea took hold. Over more beer at their favourite restaurant Bin 4, a business model developed: they could use collective buying power to reduce material cost, design sophisticated labels themselves, assemble packages of products that work syngergistically together and source the product from the exact companies overspending on advertising. Moreover it would be sold online, delivered anywhere in the world, and keep more money in everyones pockets.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e6d6522b0e7f17900ea60c1770e31cc41a48963b.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bodybuildingcooperative/our-story/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3558a7fc-91a3-475d-85f1-eebb09940aba</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 06:58:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SUPPORT SUSTAINABLE PRACTICES]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>SUPPORT SUSTAINABLE PRACTICES</h1><p>We live on Vancouver Island- so we are inidated with sustainbility messages everywhere we go. We know 30% of climate change is related to our food  system, and we know supplements sourced or produced with cheap GMO corn, soy, and wheat are not exactly helping. Being from Canada, we also believe its best we don’t inject the very cows we get our milk from with antibiotics and hormones. Maybe thats just us- but that doesnt sound very good for humans or the environment.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bodybuildingcooperative/support-sustainable-practices/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">80429d09-9855-47aa-8550-28d3fb04b4fb</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 06:44:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Do you really need fancy flavours, fillers, or packaging? Probably not. Do you really need a professional athlete on the cover of a product to convince you to buy it? That’s always cool, but again- probably not. So what do you need? You, like us, want a supplement product that is first and foremost effective, next environmentally friendly, and finally low-cost. Knowing this, we have sourced our core supplements from the best manufacturers, inputs, and companies.  Also since we have minimal costs as a cooperative, we can bring these products to you for a fraction of the cost.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bodybuildingcooperative/4c396bdb-b8fc-42cc-bb3d-7bad400fafc4/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4c396bdb-b8fc-42cc-bb3d-7bad400fafc4</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 07:53:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sharing Is Caring]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Sharing Is Caring</h1><h2>Create a unique business model that shares success amongst its members</h2><p>We are no different  than you. We too  struggle paying for necessary supplements, school fees, and beer.  That is why we too, are part of the cooperative. We are three college roommates, and more importantly regular dudes who love pumping iron but understand the costs associated with constantly working on our bodies. That is why we created a company to help deliver high quality supplements for a fraction of the cost using an innovative and unique business model developed at the University Of Victoria. Every successive member contributes to a greater collective buying power which means more savings for everyone. That is the founding idea and guiding principle. We don’t want to sleep on piles of cash like that scene in Breaking Bad, we just want to help provide a necessary service through a novel channel- a cooperative. We want to make it as easy as possible, as helpful as possible, and as pleasurable as possible so that you tell your friends. The more people we can get on board, the better it is for everyone, that is why we belong to it, and we think you should to.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bodybuildingcooperative/sharing-is-caring/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ea00b0a7-4290-434c-8d6b-010996ba65f3</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 07:51:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/323a78d7-3393-4f82-83d8-1ceb74c28de8.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bodybuildingcooperative/091a3dbe-3fec-40b9-b1c2-90a4f678ccfa/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">091a3dbe-3fec-40b9-b1c2-90a4f678ccfa</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 07:07:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/885d5962-d25c-430c-b0d7-f23bb09ef4a7.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bodybuildingcooperative/bb1cc148-5c11-449a-ae36-1a20718cb970/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bb1cc148-5c11-449a-ae36-1a20718cb970</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 07:46:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Our ZMA is the original formula created by BALCO labs in the 90s. We haven’t added anything, and we haven’t taken anything out. It is composed of the original strictly vitamins and minerals. Why? Because it is the only formula scientifically studied and anything else just taking shots in the dark.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bodybuildingcooperative/8412cbe3-ad0e-463c-8f54-825932b56194/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8412cbe3-ad0e-463c-8f54-825932b56194</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 06:43:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Our Vitamin C is……Vitamin C. Pure, plain and simple.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bodybuildingcooperative/5d6737df-32f7-44d3-a6f0-a6a42c195be5/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5d6737df-32f7-44d3-a6f0-a6a42c195be5</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 07:53:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/15e34fc7-62df-4609-a9e2-8a5461209a29.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/bodybuildingcooperative/d3b1f3b2-5db4-4805-91e4-e6497cafedfc/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d3b1f3b2-5db4-4805-91e4-e6497cafedfc</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 07:06:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>